businessinternetdirectory.com 2008-05-09

# Privacy Policy - Business Internet Directory

Privacy Policy - www.businessinternetdirectory.com 

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) is provided by **Business Internet Directory Limited** (registered company number 04225065) whose registered office is at Garforth House, 54 Micklegate, York, YO1 6LF (referred to as “us”, “our” or “we” in this Privacy Policy) for the information of visitors (referred to as “you” or “your” in this Privacy Policy) to our website, the URL of which is http://www.businessinternetdirectory.com (.co.uk, .net, .org.uk, .org, .ltd.uk, .tv), referred to as the “Website” in this Privacy Policy.

By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. If you object to this use and disclosure please do not register for a Priority Advert with us. If you object to your information being featured on our database in a Standard Entry, please contact us, in accordance with Clause 10 of this Policy, in order to arrange its removal. 

**1 Privacy**  
We wish to demonstrate our firm commitment to your rights to privacy. This is why we have set out the privacy guidelines set out below. We may need to change this Privacy Policy over time. We will post changes to this Privacy Policy to the Website when such changes are necessary. All amended terms shall automatically be effective immediately after they are initially posted on the Website.

**2 Law**  
The information contained in this Privacy Policy shall be governed and construed in accordance with English law and be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts.

**3 Data Protection Act**  
Business Internet Directory Limited has notified the Information Commissioner under the terms of the Data Protection Act 1998 that it may obtain information about data subjects.

**4 Information that we hold**

**(A) Information gathered by us - _Collected information_**

_Business Internet Directory Standard Free Entry_

I. You will appreciate that we may need to gather some information about you in order to compile our business directory. This information may include:  
(i) Company/business name  
(ii) Company/business address  
(iii) telephone number  
(iv) A category for your business

The information we collect will then be featured in the Business Internet Directory as a Standard Free Entry and will be made available to users of our Website when they search our database. We may also use the information we collect to contact you about our Priority Advert and other services which we offer. 

_Business Internet Directory Priority Advert_

II. You will appreciate that may need to gather some information from you when you wish to register to use our Priority Advertisement Service. This information may include: __

(i) contact forename and surname  
(ii) Company/business name  
(iii) Company/business address  
(iv) telephone number  
(v) fax number  
(vi) e-mail address  
(vii) website address  
(viii) payment details  
(ix) A category for your business  
(x) Keywords that describe your business offering

The information you provide (excepting your payment details) will then be featured in the Business Internet Directory as a Priority Advert and will be made available to users of our Website when they search our database. The information in your Priority Advert will be given priority over the other Standard Free Entry in the database and will be displayed along with a map, e mail and web address hyperlinks. We may also use the information you provide to contact you about other services which we provide and to contact you should we encounter any problems in the provisions of services to you. 

III. We may, on occasions, collect additional personal information from surveys on the Website, which you will not be obliged to fill in or return to us.

IV. We also collect demographic and profile data on the Website. This information may be combined with other forms of information to permit us to bring together, in aggregate form, information about the people who use the Website. Such information will enable us to understand, in general terms, user preferences in relation to the content of the Website and the effectiveness of the advertising.

**(B) Information that is automatically logged - _Stored Information_**

I. Your IP address  
When you enter the Website, we use your internet protocol (“IP”) address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Website and to help identify you. We also have the ability to ascertain what type of operating system and browser software you use and to identify the geographical location of your browser. Your IP address is also used by us to gather broad demographic information and other purposes, such as monitoring visitor frequency. 

II. Cookies  
You may be aware that there is a technology called “cookies”. Cookies are small files that are transferred from the Website to the hard drive of your computer and which help us to provide you with customised services. A cookie will not allow us obtain information of a personal nature that will identify you to us, such as your name and address. We will only be aware of such information if you provide the information to us or you have set the preferences in your browser to provide this information automatically.  
Most cookies are "session cookies", which means that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session using the Website. If your browser permits you to do so, you may decline our cookies. Please note that if you decline our cookies you may not be able to use certain features on the Website.  
You may also encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Website that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

III. What we do with the stored information that we collect  
The information we collect via the Website in aggregate form allows us to carry out an analysis of user behaviour in general. This enables us to measure overall interest in the Website and helps us to develop the Website to make it more interesting/useful to users in general terms. Such information also enables us to inform advertisers how many users have clicked on to the various advertisements displayed on the Website. The analysis we perform does not include any personal information provided by you. We merely use the aggregate form of the information for these purposes. We will not provide any personal information you have disclosed to us to any third party unless you give us specific authority to do so. 

**5 Sharing collected or stored information**  
5.1 Any information that is gathered from visitors to or customers of the Website is not sold, made available to, or otherwise distributed to third parties for any purpose. We will not share personal information about you unless we have your specific permission to do so.

5.2 We share the information we gather via the Website with advertisers and other partners. The information we share comprises information in aggregate form only (Stored information). 

**6 Telling you what information we hold about you**  
If you wish to know what information we hold on you, please contact us in writing supplying sufficient information to enable us to identify you. We will only send this information to the e-mail address we have on file, unless you send us your postal address and request that we send the information to you at your postal address (and we are able to verify the validity of this address).

**7 Removing and correcting information**  
If you request to remove your personal information from our database or you wish us to amend or change the information we hold about you on our database, we will remove or amend any such information on your request. 

**8 Data quality**  
You may change and modify the information you have previously provided to us, as follows: 

8.1 Send an e-mail to us at:

| 

---|---  
  
8.2 Call us on:

| 

01904 601011  
  
8.3 Send a letter to:

| 

Business Internet Directory Limited  
Garforth House  
54 Micklegate  
York  
North Yorkshire  
YO1 6LF  
  
**9 Other Collectors of Information**  
Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies. Since we do not control the privacy policy of any third party, you are subject to the privacy policy of that third party.

**10 Contact us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, how we run the Website or your dealing with our Website, please send an e-mail to us at [mail@businessinternetdirectory.com](mailto:mail@businessinternetdirectory.com)
